<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<root>
  <TEXT><![CDATA[


Record date: 2087-08-15

EDVISIT^43294739^FINNEY, INDIANA^08/15/87^NARANJO, KENNETH

The patient was seen and examined in the Emergency Department on

08/15/2087.  The patient was seen by Dr. Kaminski.  I have discussed

the management with her.  I have also seen the patient personally

and reviewed the medical record.  This is an addendum to the

medical record.

HISTORY OF PRESENT ILLNESS:  This is a 50-year-old female who is

sent in by her primary doctor after having had EKG changes today.

 Her history, which I personally obtained and in review of the

record, she has a history of sarcoidosis, recently has had

increased cough and some shortness of breath, given albuterol

with symptomatic improvement yesterday and returned today with

some persistent pain, which she says is generally related to

cough.  She has had no fevers, chills, or shortness of breath.

REVIEW OF SYSTEMS:  As indicated and otherwise negative.  She is

asymptomatic at this time.  She has had no recent travel.

PAST MEDICAL HISTORY:  Diabetes.

SOCIAL HISTORY:  She is a nonsmoker.

PHYSICAL EXAMINATION:  The patient is very well appearing,

pleasant and in no acute distress.  Her vital signs are stable. 

She is normocephalic, atraumatic.  Pharynx and ENT is normal. 

Neck is supple and nontender.  Chest is clear.  Heart is regular

with normal pulses.  Abdomen is soft and nontender without masses

that are appreciated.  Skin is warm and dry.  She has no CVA

tenderness, no back tenderness.  She is awake, alert, and

oriented.  Sensory and motor exam are normal.

ASSESSMENT AND PLAN:  This is a woman who complains of having had

some chest discomfort.  She has a history of sarcoid and has EKG,

which I reviewed, which shows lateral T-wave changes as suggested

by her referring doctor.  She is pain free.  Initial lab results

show hematocrit of 40, INR of 1, and a troponin which was

negative.

Plan at this time is for hospital admission to rule out MI given

her EKG change.  She looks clinically stable.

______________________________

NARANJO, KENNETH M.D.

D: 08/15/87

T: 08/15/87

Dictated By: NARANJO, KENNETH

eScription document:3-7918390 BFFocus

******** Not reviewed by Attending Physician ********





]]></TEXT>
  <TAGS>
    <FAMILY_HIST id="DOC2" indicator="not present">
      <FAMILY_HIST id="F0" indicator="not present"/>
      <FAMILY_HIST id="F1" indicator="not present"/>
      <FAMILY_HIST id="F2" indicator="not present"/>
    </FAMILY_HIST>
    <SMOKER id="DOC4" status="never">
      <SMOKER id="S0" start="1065" end="1074" text="nonsmoker" status="never" comment=""/>
      <SMOKER id="S1" start="1065" end="1075" text="nonsmoker." status="never" comment=""/>
      <SMOKER id="S2" start="1065" end="1074" text="nonsmoker" status="never" comment=""/>
    </SMOKER>
    <DIABETES id="DOC0" time="before DCT" indicator="mention">
      <DIABETES id="D0" start="1028" end="1036" text="Diabetes" time="before DCT" indicator="mention" comment=""/>
      <DIABETES id="D1" start="1028" end="1036" text="Diabetes" time="before DCT" indicator="mention" comment=""/>
      <DIABETES id="D2" start="1028" end="1036" text="Diabetes" time="before DCT" indicator="mention" comment=""/>
    </DIABETES>
    <DIABETES id="DOC1" time="during DCT" indicator="mention">
      <DIABETES id="D3" start="1028" end="1036" text="Diabetes" time="during DCT" indicator="mention" comment=""/>
      <DIABETES id="D4" start="1028" end="1036" text="Diabetes" time="during DCT" indicator="mention" comment=""/>
      <DIABETES id="D5" start="1028" end="1036" text="Diabetes" time="during DCT" indicator="mention" comment=""/>
    </DIABETES>
    <DIABETES id="DOC3" time="after DCT" indicator="mention">
      <DIABETES id="D6" start="1028" end="1036" text="Diabetes" time="after DCT" indicator="mention" comment=""/>
      <DIABETES id="D7" start="1028" end="1036" text="Diabetes" time="after DCT" indicator="mention" comment=""/>
      <DIABETES id="D8" start="1028" end="1036" text="Diabetes" time="after DCT" indicator="mention" comment=""/>
    </DIABETES>
  </TAGS>
</root>
